brainbuxa.com 2012-09-06

# Brain Buxa

#### Privacy & Policy 

BrainBuxa members have the complete flexibility to modify / remove their information. However, certain information like your email address, mobile and username may not be modifiable for the functionality of the site. However, a member will be able to delete his/her profile completely. If for any reason you wish to remove some information and have difficulty in doing so please contact us on – privacy[@]brainbuxa.comPolicy Updates :-We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our homepage. 

Privacy Policy:-  
---  
    
BrainBuxa is an online and mobile centric service that allows Users to build and leverage their network of Friends. BrainBuxa Members can view each others' profiles, communicate with friends, create or join Community, share study material, photos, videos, post comments, blog, send messages and call friends.  
At BrainBuxa, we respect and take steps to protect the privacy of our Users  
The disclosure of personal information is always a sensitive issue and the BrainBuxa team takes it very seriously.   
We consider it our highest priority to protect the privacy of our members. This privacy policy outlines the types of information BrainBuxa collects and how that information is used in the operation of the site.  
We do everything we reasonably can to protect your rights of privacy on systems and websites controlled by us, but we are not liable for any unauthorised or unlawful disclosures of your personal and confidential information made by third parties who are not subject to our control, for example advertisers and websites that have links to our Site. You should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours.  
    
How BrainBuxa Uses Your Personal Information:-  
To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other visitors and members, which allows our users to identify each other and expand their network. Bharat student members can change their profile information at any time.   
This policy covers how BrainBuxa treats personal information that BrainBuxa collects and receives, including information related to your past use of BrainBuxa products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.  
    
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE:-  
    
General  
BrainBuxa collects personal information when you register with BrainBuxa. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, mobile, personal interests, demographic data and other such information to authenticate users as well as to send Email and Mobile notifications relating to the users activity on the site. All the other information submission is left to the members’ discretion. BrainBuxa automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, cookieinformation, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request.  
    
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies:-  
Some of our Web pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Web user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. The information stored will be used to provide enhanced experience for the user.   
You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter your original user ID and password to gain access to certain parts of the Web site and some sections of the site would not work.   
Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; click stream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience. We may also analyze information that does not contain Personal Information for trends and statistics.   
    
Third Party Links :-  
BrainBuxa may contain links to third party websites. BrainBuxa is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on BrainBuxa.  
    
Information security:-  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, including appropriate encryption and physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.  
We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.  
    
INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE:-  
BrainBuxa does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
  
  * ? We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with BrainBuxa under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help BrainBuxa communicate with you about offers from BrainBuxa and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information
  * ? We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing BrainBuxa to collect and use their child's information without consenting to BrainBuxa sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes.
  * ? We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * ? We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BrainBuxa's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * ? We transfer information about you if BrainBuxa is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, BrainBuxa will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

BrainBuxa displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.  
  
  * ? BrainBuxa does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
  * ? BrainBuxa advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

BrainBuxa works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. For more information regarding providers of products or services that you've requested please read our detailed reference links.  
    
Updating Information :-  
    
Third Party Advertising :-  
Ads can be of two kinds - (1) Those that belong to BrainBuxa.com, or (2) Those that belong to third party advertisers. The third party advertisers may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about whether you, or others who are using your computer, viewed their advertisements and determine which ads were clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BrainBuxa.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any third-party advertisers.  
If you have questions or suggestions email us at [info@brainbuxa.com](mailto:info@brainbuxa.com)
